It lasted 30 days... You will remember it as long as you live.
Voyage of the Damned is a drama, war film directed by Stuart Rosenberg.
A luxury liner carries Jewish refugees from Hitler's
Germany in a desperate fight for survival.
Denise Kreisler, played by Faye Dunaway.
Professor Egon Kreisler, played by Oskar Werner.
Lili Rosen, played by Lee Grant.
Carl Rosen, played by Sam Wanamaker.
Anna Rosen, played by Lynne Frederick.
Joseph Joseph, played by David de Keyser.
Voyage of the Damned is a 1976 drama film directed by Stuart Rosenberg, with an all-star cast featuring Faye
Dunaway, Oskar Werner, Lee Grant, Max von Sydow, James Mason, Lynne Frederick and Malcolm McDowell.
The story was inspired by actual events concerning
the fate of the ocean liner MS St.
Louis carrying Jewish refugees from Germany to Cuba in 1939.
It was based on a 1974 nonfiction book of the same title
written by Gordon Thomas and Max Morgan-Witts.
The screenplay was written by Steve Shagan and David Butler.
The film was produced by ITC Entertainment and released by Rank Film
Distributors in the UK and Avco Embassy Pictures in the U.S.
The film explores themes of nazi, escape, holocaust
(shoah), world war ii, jew persecution.
The tone is emotional.